Okay. Hey, how's it going guys? I just
put together a mirrorboard that explains
step by step how my business works so
that you can understand very easily. And
I've included a lot of images and
screenshots so that you can see exactly
what I'm doing just so that it makes
more sense. I've spent a lot of time
making this so I'll be breaking down
each step for you. So there are five
main sections. The first section tells
my story. Second shows you a bunch of
case studies and examples of posts, how
much they're making. Step three shows
how you can do it. Step four shows the
technical side of this, how to use Tweet
Hunter to make posts and make it a lot
easy for you. And then step five shows
my students results. Step six shows what
I offer. So let's begin. I've put in a
lot of time, so I hope that this would
be very helpful for you guys. So let's
begin. For for those of you who don't
know who I am, I am 22 and I started
this business around 2 years ago. And so
how it started out was I was in college
and I was around 18 to 20. This was in
the years of 2021 to 2023. I never had
more than $100 in the bank. And so I was
basically a broke college student. I
couldn't afford basics like food or bed
sheets or any of that sort of stuff. And
I also got into a car accident and I
nearly died. So this was a very low
point in my life. And so over the next
few years or just a year, I've tried
building businesses. I wanted to make
money online because I thought that that
would be the only way for me to survive
and succeed in this world. So I tried
and failed 8 to 10 different businesses
such as drop shipping, flipping cars,
websites, YouTube, Tik Tok, selling
furniture, Etsy, but none of those
really worked. Well, definitely not
enough to make a survivable income. So
this was a year where I was spending at
least 12 hours per day every day for a
year straight just experimenting trying
everything and I've had so many failures
so little success but I' I've learned a
lot and I basically there were takeaways
from each different business and
failures. So after around a year or so I
had my first breakthrough. So I had my
first sale in October of 2023. Uh it's
not shown here, but after I got my first
sale of $10, it was basically selling a
software uh for $10. And then around 2
months later uh in January, I had my
first 2K profit day and then so from
there growth has been exponential. So
from there start making thousands of
dollars per day. Uh and of course my
lifestyle changed as well. So, this was
my first time um driving a Lamborghini.
And these are some pictures that I've
taken. So, yeah. Uh basically a 180
within a year or two. And I want to show
you guys how I did it. Be completely
honest and transparent um about myself
and how my business works. So, yeah,
we've done millions of dollars in cash
collected. $15 million, more than that.
Not all of it goes to me. I split it
with my partners a lot. But you do see
here that within the past around 5
months, I've personally netted myself
$1.8 million of cash collected. So,
which is almost two for myself within
the past 5 months. So, this is my Stripe
dashboard. And then, so going to step
two of case studies. So, I want to show
you basically real examples of Twitter
accounts and posts that we've made that
have gotten lots of views and how many
comments, how many leads they've
generated, how many sales each of them
have generated. So, uh just as a
disclaimer, I have dozens and dozens of
accounts. So, these are just a few
accounts that I have uh showing you.
First is example, we are teaching people
how to do e-commerce. So essentially all
the content that we post is about uh how
to make money, teaching people about
business, how to make money through
different topics and niches. So for
example, this one we have e-commerce,
this one we have AI models, this one we
have websites, here we have sweep
stakes. So we're teaching people uh
these skills and we're selling ebooks,
courses, services, coachings, anything
that is digital that helps people learn
about business and grow and make money.
Basically, so this account, for example,
is teaching people how to do e-commerce.
You can see that the posts themselves
are very, very simple. It takes only a
few seconds, maybe like 15 or 20 seconds
to make to type all of this out. And it
generates tens of thousands of views.
And each one generates, you know, many
comments, 241 comments. This one
generates 448 comments. This one
generates 197 comments. And the reason
why comments are important is because
each comment represents a lead. So
whenever someone either comments or
likes on these posts, they will
automatically receive a DM. Basically uh
they'll receive like a free guide or a
link to a checkout link or just any
link. And um
a small fraction of them will convert
into sales and purchases. So that's
what's important. Basically, we make
these posts and say we have an
eye-catching header and then we post a
bunch of details and then they always
have a CTA, a call to action saying if
you want this full course or full guide
and if you want to learn obviously it's
for free. All you have to do is like and
comment and you'll get it. So, anyone
who comments or likes they will receive
the free guide or free course. So, the
comments the number of comments equals
the number of people who receive these
free guides and free courses. So you can
see the hundreds of them are getting it
per post and a small fraction will buy
uh a course or an ebook or whatever
digital product for anywhere between a
few hundred to $10,000 or $20,000. So
for example, we might be selling a
$3,000 course and let's say that 241
comments generally realistically
conservatively three sales of 2 or
$3,000 that's nearly 10k per post. So
here is another example and of course
per account we're doing thousands of
posts. This is another account number
two. This topic and niche is about AI
models. So teaching people how to make
money with AI models. So uh just as a
disclaimer for these accounts I partner
with experienced entrepreneurs. So for
example, this guy is actually I'm
partnering with a friend who is very
successful with e-commerce and he's
providing the knowledge and experience
and expertise, skills and proof and I'm
the one who's helping uh creating the
content. I'm making the post get lots of
views and make sales for what we're
selling. So it's like a partnership
model. I work with each one of these
people. You know, this is another guy.
he's experienced and successful in with
AI models. So essentially it's kind of
like um like Only Fans except you know
it's like more models is there's less of
an NSFW but we're posting a lot of you
know these attractive models and uh you
know they get lots of views and you know
a fraction of them will end up
subscribing per month so we make a lot
of money doing that. Parker himself has
made millions of dollars doing this. So
you know basically I'm the partner here
again. So just to show you this is the
account and we have a free discord
community where we have lots of free
courses and guides. So you can see here
this is the discord and inside these are
links to the free guides and free course
that we have. People go through them
people learn and grow and they become
successful with this business and these
are for free. So once they learn a lot,
we provide lots of value and then you
know if they're interested in mentorship
from Parker then they apply here. We've
had 1,800 people apply to Parker's
mentorship and then out of that we've
had 577 calls uh with people who were
interested. And then out of that 577
there were 132 sales of on average 4.3K.
So, we were actually charging $5,000 for
the mentorship. But, you know, for some
people, we made sales. We gave
discounts. So, that's why uh it got to
4.3K on average. And so, we've made 570K
uh net profits cash collected from this
one account. Just so you know, we only
have this had this account active for
around 3 months. So, within the 3month
period, we did 570K, which is nearly
200k per month in profits. And of
course, Parker and I, we do a 50-50
split. I take 50% of it, you know, he
takes 50% of it. So, since we made 50K
total, I walked away with myself with
around almost 3K and he did, you know,
basically the same. So, showing you a
bunch of tweets. So, this one is
basically giving information and details
about this business so that people are
scrolling on Twitter and they see this
post, right? And then, so this one gets
37,000 views, 164 comments. And so from
this one sale, from this one post we
make six sales. We generate $27,000.
So you can see that per post we're
making five figures in profits. This is
another post. It got 15,000 views and
112 comments. We got four sales from
this. $20,000. So, you know, the
interesting thing is that, you know,
people will look at these tweets and
they're saying, "Oh, that's not a lot of
views. you know, Instagram, Tik Tok,
we're getting millions of views and
people sleep on Twitter just because,
you know, we're getting very little
views, but they don't see that the
conversion is very high. And the reason
why the conversion is high is because
people on Twitter are very intelligent.
They're intelligent, they're very
ambitious, they tend to be entrepreneurs
already, and they have a lot of capital.
So that's why even with very few views
just by the way we're targeting very
high quality people and the conversion
rate is pretty good. So that's why we're
making so much money despite getting
very little views compared to other
platforms. So this is why Twitter uh aka
X is underrated is because no one knows
that these posts that are getting so few
views are making so much money. And this
is per post by the way. You know, this
one got 10 sales of $42,000. And
unfortunately, I had to terminate and
discontinue this business just because
it conflicts with my moral boundaries.
So, this has been discontinued. But
nevertheless, we have dozens and dozens
of accounts like these in different
topics and categories and niches. So,
this is another account I want to show
you. This is a very small account. It
looks like it's dead, but Casey teaches
people about websites. he's successful
with it. Uh he gives out a free course,
a free ebook, 14 pages and it shows
people how to do this business so people
learn uh once again and once they go
through it, you know, people become
interested uh to learn more. They want
more value. They want more help. So he
offers a 10K mentorship. Again, we're
doing 50/50 split. So per sale, we get
5K each. This one post only gets 5,000
views but gets 42 comments. Three people
buy for $30,000.
This post only 6k views, 26 comments.
Two people buy for 20k. So you think
that, you know, these posts are dead,
but in reality they're making so much.
So that's account number three. Account
number four, uh this is my friend who's
experienced with sweep stakes. He's an
affiliate. He's, you know, he's very
successful with it. So what we do is we
teach people about the business, how it
works. But we we help people make money
with it. So he has a discord server
where you know he teaches people he has
a community and uh he has a bunch of
free resources for people to learn from
free guides free courses and he charges
you know mentorship and basically we've
made more than $700,000. So you know
this is an example 162,000 views 1.4k 4K
comments, almost 100k views, 570
comments. Just out of these comments,
you know, every single person who either
likes or comments gets the free courses,
the free guides, right? And even if a
tiny percentage, even if only 0.3
people, 0.3% of people end up buying,
we're still making thousands or tens of
thousands of dollars per post selling
these things. So, this is how my
business works. And you know, you might
be wondering, how could I possibly do
this when I don't have these kinds of
experience or statistics or proof or you
know, business success to work off of.
So in that case, I have a solution for
you. A lot of mente students, a lot of
them are making five figures profits per
month. You know, many of them are making
30K, 50K, K per month. And I would say
that half of those students who are
making lots of money have no business
experience whatsoever. So I'll show you
exactly the workar around and what
they're doing to do this of course
morally and ethically and right that's
actually providing huge value and
benefit to people. So you know getting
back into it I have more than 50
accounts that are doing this. Some of
the best performing accounts are not
shown in the case studies but it was
just to show you how it works.
So um yeah we have thousands of posts
that are each making so much money. We
have niches in ecom, YouTube, sports
betting, AI, and many, many other
topics. So, you know, you can see that
they're getting lots of views on my main
account included. We're getting lots of
engagement. And then you can see that
we've been making, you know, lots of
posts and then
$15 million in cash collecting within
the past two years. Most accounts that
you see uh on Twitter, you know, that
are saying comment this to get this free
guide. I would guarantee that around
half or more of all those posts that you
see belong to me or my partners. So,
we're responsible for a lot of those.
We're getting millions of views
regularly. And so, you know, you might
not even realize, but you're seeing my
posts every single day. And for those
who, you know, want to work with me, I
provide retweets and shout outs for my
big account. So you know the difficult
thing about this business is just that
getting started when you're starting
with zero followers or you know account
from zero it's very difficult to get
views on your post it's very difficult
so what I do is I have lots of big
accounts and I retweet from all these
big accounts your post so instantly you
know thousands of people who are
following these accounts each one of
them view your post and so you know
immediately you can go viral let's say
five big accounts are retweeting you,
boosting you, giving you shout outs,
then you know you can go viral very
easily. So you know that is what I do
when I create new accounts. That is
exactly what I do. I retweet from all
the big accounts so that that new post
from the new account goes to viral
instantly and then after that you know
once you get your first viral post it's
very easy to get views after that. So,
you know, students and partners and
myself included, we basically, you know,
go viral within just a few days versus
someone working by themselves for more
than 6 months. So, moving to the next
step, it is difficult when you don't
have business experience like how can I
make these kinds of bold claims and
stats and proofs when I don't have
anything myself. So, that's the biggest
problem. And so, there are a few
different ways to work around this.
Actually, there's two options. I want to
go over option two first actually. This
is the most common and most recommended
method which is where you partner with
successful millionaire entrepreneurs. So
you know I have hundreds of these kinds
of friends. I have a huge network of
successful people, friends with a lot of
them. So you choose one person you want
to work with. For example, a YouTuber
with 16 million subscribers. You know I
have a friend who is exactly that. I
have a friend who's making more than $5
million per year in e-commerce. I have
some friends who are making nine figures
per year. I have some friends who are
doing, you know, eight figures in real
estate. So, I have a lot of successful
friends and you can partner with one of
them. And the issue with them is that,
you know, they're successful with their
business, but they don't have any time
to, you know, make posts on Twitter and
sell digital products. So, that's where
you come in is that is you do all the
work for them. You make posts for them.
You leverage their knowledge and
expertise and their proofs and their
success. You post them on their behalf
because they don't have time. You're
doing all the work for them. You make
the posts for them. You get millions of
views and you drive sales to the courses
and whatever they're selling. So, for
example, you know, let's say that you
end up working with a YouTuber with 60
million subscribers and then he makes,
let's say, like 500K uh per month. Then
uh you can make posts, you know,
basically saying how we did this, how
we're making this much money, uh
basically giving people free sauce,
business methods, secret tips and stuff
like that. And as a result, you'll start
getting lots of views. And then, you
know, let's say that he's selling a 5K
coaching program. And then uh let's say,
you know, get you get 30% which is 15K
or you get like 50% which is, you know,
25K per sale. So maybe, you know, you're
getting two or three sales per week,
which is, you know, around uh 10 to 15K
per week, but you're getting half of
that. So you're getting like 5 to 7.5K
per week, which is the equivalent of 20
to 30K net profits for yourself per
month. And of course, you can keep
scaling and uh growing that. So you're
earning more each month. So that's the
thing is that you can leverage their
authority and success to easily get
millions of views. And this is a
win-win. No, you're teaching people,
you're helping people grow and learn
from these successful entrepreneurs and
you yourself, you're making money as
well, right? And the partners, they're
uh making money as well and they're
getting their influence out there. So,
it's a win-win for everyone. The other
option, which is the affiliates method,
is that basically you take one of my
products that I already have built.
Instead of, you know, you creating a
product from zero and spending a lot of
time on it and guess what people want, I
have products, ebooks, courses, stuff
like that that already have proven to
sell hundreds or thousands of copies.
So, you don't need to guess what the
demand is. I'll just give it to you so
that it's a lot easier and that way it's
a much smaller learning curve. This way,
you don't have to start from zero. It's
a lot easier for you. So, for example, I
have an ebook on AI automation, teaching
me people about AI automation, and it's
selling $700 per sale, per copy. It has
270 pages, and it teaches business
owners um about AI automation. So, you
know, it's a huge win. It teaches
business owners how to save um hundreds,
tens or hundreds of thousands of dollars
with AI. So, it's huge value. And this
has sold, you know, hundreds of copies.
So, I recommend taking either of these
approaches if you have no business
experience and you can be making these
kinds of posts, garnering lots of views
and lots of leads and making lots of
sales.
So again, around half of my students
making five figures per month in profits
have zero business experience. So that
is these are the two approaches that
they take. Uh this is coming soon. Okay.
So now I'm going to go over how to do
all this the backend the technical
aspect. So you must use Tweet Hunter.
And so you're probably wondering what it
does. Basically I'm going to show you
the secret cheat code of how this
business works and how it makes it so
easy for me. So essentially Tweet Hunter
is a software that allows you to
automate and schedule posts in advance.
And it also allows you to AI generate
hundreds of posts in just seconds. You
can generate hundreds of posts and
schedule them in advance. So let's say
like you make 300 posts in like 5
minutes, right? Let's say that you
generate that much and then you schedule
in advance. You make 10 posts today. You
schedule 10 posts for tomorrow. You
schedule 10 posts for the day after
that. So that you do all the work right
now and all the posting is automated and
scheduled so that it just posts even
when you're sleeping. It's on autopilot.
So you can do that every single day. And
most importantly, it will automatically
send any link or any message to everyone
who either comments or likes on your
post uh via DM. So for example, let's
say that your post gets 800 likes, which
is common, average, and then you know,
Tweet Hunter will automatically and
instantly send a checkout link to all
800s of these people. And let's say
you're selling like an $500 course,
right? You're sending that to 800 people
who comment on your post asking for it.
And then uh let's say that's only 10 of
800 people end up buying. So you're
getting 10 sales of $500 each, which is
5K from one post. So you know, that's
just one example. And you really cannot
do this business without Tweet Hunter. I
mean, you can, but it's like a 100 times
more difficult. Here is the link to join
Tweet Hunter. If you're on this
mirrorboard, you can just click right
here and you can get set up. The first
seven days are free, so you can do this
trial. So now now that you have Twiggy
Hunter, this business should be very
easy and you can just generate and make
posts within seconds within one hour.
You can uh generate all of them and
schedule in advance and all the
marketing efforts taken care of on your
behalf. So for example, you can take
care of them a month's work worth of
content within just a few minutes or
like an hour. And obviously it's only
going to send them the DM if they ask
for it. So either if they comment or
like on the post, they're going to get
it. So, it's obviously it's not going to
spam or send unsolicited messages.
Um, and it's pretty common for for a
tweet hunter to send to more than a
thousand people per day in a DMs. You
can see example of what my DMs look
like. This is the reason why I never
reply on Twitter is just because I'm
sending out thousands of DMs every day.
So, you just send something, it's just
going to be buried like so far
underneath. This is what it looks like
per day. I have to scroll so much to
basically get to any DM. So, for
example, if you sent me a message
yesterday, I have to spend basically a
long time scrolling to see and find your
message. So, that's why I never reply
there or very rarely. And so, now I'm
going to go over um basically
the success that my students have had
being honest and how they're doing. So
on my YouTube, I do have uh so far just
two YouTube interviews. These are like
20 or 30 minutes each. These students
have each
uh been successful making at least, you
know, $1,000 profits per day. Uh so you
can go through these YouTube videos.
They basically explain their entire
journey of start to finish. you know the
journey, the difficulties that they've
had, the troubles, you know, the
failures, every single detail so that
you can basically get a sense of what
the process is like just for full
transparency and so you can see you know
what the journey has been like because a
lot of coaches will show the end results
or just testimonials or proof but I want
you guys to understand the every detail
of what the student goes through when I
coach them in my mentorship program. So
fortunately I have a lot of successful
students right now. I have 454. I
actually I think I have more. I have
around 60 students right now and so you
can get talk to any of them. You can
talk to any of them. Uh a lot of them
have been successful. For example, you
know Zayn he joined in May. He was
actually working at a cafe working
minimum wage before he joined. He saved
up a lot working at the cafe and then he
started seeing a lot of success. So he's
making a lot per month now. So you can
you can click on this talk to with him.
Kbot is another example. Um well I'm not
revealing his name just because they
want to stay anonymous and private but
you can still message them. So they're
still making a lot. Kbot joined a little
later than Zayn but nevertheless they're
making a lot of money right here each
one of them. Okay. So some Discord wins.
So K he bought a G Wagon Mercedes K
MSRP. He bought it used for around
$57,000
full in cash. So this is his post. It's
a big win. I'm pretty happy about that.
This is after his results of joining my
program. He started making lots of sales
every month. So this is his win. Yeah.
Just more wins of, you know, students
capturing payments. So this guy was
sharing was selling a $500 mentorship or
something. He's been making multiple of
these sales. More students making their
first $1,000 sales. Um, this is a
student that made So, basically, this
student sent me $900. And the reason why
is because I do a profit split with my
students. So, whenever they make a sale
or money, they will send a small
fraction of it to me. So, for example,
uh, this sale was $3,000 and, you know,
he sends me $900. So, we both make
money. So, he keeps the rest of the 2.1K
for himself. Um, I'll share more about
this later about the profit splitting.
But the whole idea is that the reason
why I do this profit split is because I
want both of us to win. I will help you
genuinely more and there will be an
incentive for me to help you and
actually make money and become
successful with this profit split. So
that's the and that's basically the gist
of it. Before I just sold this
mentorship, but now we do the profit
split and you know even with the profit
split, they're actually making a lot
more money now. So again, more details
on that later. More sales from students,
more sales from students, more sales
from students. This was funny because I
think it was the same day. I was like,
"Trust me, you're going to get your
first 1K uh payment soon." Like
literally the day of or the the day
after he gets that. So I was pretty
proud of him for that. And then so you
know, there's basically hundreds of
these kinds of testimonials. I just
included a few of them. But anyways,
yeah, moving on to what I'm providing
for my mentorship program. Obviously,
I'm not trying to sell this. Uh it's
just like an opportunity for you. If you
are interested and you you like the idea
of it, then I'm always welcome to take
on a bunch of new students given that
you're qualified. I do have hundreds of
people who do want to join this every
week. So, I'm very selective of who I
let in. Generally, I have less than like
a two or 3% acceptance rate just because
I only accept the highest quality
students inside. And I'll go over this
more in detail later, but generally
I only accept the hardest working people
and those who, you know, can actually be
committed, dedicated, serious about this
business. And the reason why is because
I want to take in just a few select high
performing individuals than you know
having like a hundred or hundreds of uh
just normal students so that I can focus
more time and energy on just a select
few students and they can make a lot of
money uh and because they deserve my
full attention and focus and my health.
So that is uh it. So, you know, just as
a disclaimer, I do have very uh high
standards of who I let in. So, you know,
I want you to imagine you have five X
accounts. Each one is automated making
posts uh while you're sleeping. You're
getting hundreds of thousands of views
per day across these accounts, making
these posts, hundreds of comments daily,
and a small fraction of them turn into
sales of few hundred or few thousand
each. So, let's say you're getting three
to 10 sales of products that are priced
between 500 to 2,000 per day. So, you're
making a lot. So, I want you to imagine
this. Um, and this is essentially what I
do, but you know, on a much bigger
scale, 100x. So, the purpose of this
mentorship is pretty simple, to help you
make a lot of money within a few months
selling digital products. And that is
the goal and also the expectation for
each of my students. So I expect each
student who comes in to make at least
five figures per per month in profits.
So you know what's included is that I
serve both as a mentor and a business
partner, not just a coach. Give you the
methods to how I get hundreds of
thousands of views per post. Give you
templates and everything you need. How
to convert those millions of views into
sales. I'll be providing one-on-one
daily communication via text and calls
if you schedule and let me know in
advance. You get complete community
access uh to all the students in the
discord making five figures per month in
profits. So you can work with them um
collaborate, learn from them, do
whatever you like. So it's completely
open. There is no restrictions. Just
don't scam or annoy people or spam. Uh
just general stuff and do whatever you
like. Um whatever resources, take
advantage of everything to make money. I
have four I have 50 course modules in
here. Um, I'm so used to saying 40
something because I keep adding more and
more force modules every single week. It
basically covers everything that you
need to know about the business model so
that you can learn.
I'll go over more details on this later.
So, I'll also be teaching you how to
automate the entire back end so that
you're generating sales and views even
during your sleep working. So, because
that's the ultimate goal, right? You
want to be making a lot but also at the
same time you don't want to be working
constantly. You can automate it and
systematize.
So yeah, I'll basically be giving you
all case studies,
breakdowns or whatever you need. So here
are the steps uh once you join what
you'll be getting how it works. So first
you join uh you get access to the
program. You get 50 course modules. Um,
again, I'll be going over more of the
details in a bit. And then you can
start, we can both start posting
immediately. So, uh, I'll help you make
viral tweets. Um, you can draft a bunch
and I can polish, you know, give you
feedback and we can post them. We may
build your product if you don't have one
already together. And we will focus on
turning uh, views into sales. So, we'll
just keep improving over time, getting
millions of views. Of course, it might
take a while, but we will get there.
Just keep improving and scaling. So, in
the beginning, you might only be getting
like 500k views, like a few thousand in
sales, but then each time you learn
every day, you're learning and growing.
So, you can only keep increasing the
number that you're making each month.
So, 10K, 30K, 50K, uh, and etc. So I
also want to go over why I want to teach
you what I benefit. So most people do
benefit from the upfront fee uh you know
basically charging people to get in
which of course I do as well but for me
that is not the main incentive. The
benefits I want to be transparent just
so that uh what I'm in here for. So
basically the main goal for me is a
profit split. So for example, I might
take 25% of all your profits. So
example, if you make 10K per month, I'll
take 2.5K. If you make 50K, then I'll
take 12.5K.
So if you don't make money, then I don't
make money for myself. I only benefit
when you win. So that's why I want each
and every one of my students to succeed
and make money because if you do, I also
benefit for myself. So that's why my
students are seeing faster results and
higher profits than any other program
that I've ran or that other people have
been in. So that's why the success rate
is so high is because I'm so invested in
each and every one of my students
genuinely. So going back to the 50
course modules that I was talking about
earlier, these are just a bunch of stuff
that I cover in it. I'm not going to go
over all of this in this video just
because it would take too much time and
I don't feel like it. So this you can
just read this on your on your own. Um I
have a lot 50. Um I only got to 32 just
cuz I was too lazy. I don't want to
include all the other ones. But there
are 50 modules in there and um yeah you
you'll get all that. So that's a course.
It's kind of like a 4-year degree but
instead learning how to operate this
business. So you'll be learning a lot.
Everything that I know that I have in my
brain regarding this business you'll
absorb and learn.
So once you're done with that, um, oh
yeah, I also have some bonus stuff. So
I've made $2.6 million with my software
business. So I'll show you how I did
that, how I market, how I made the post,
how everything's done if you'd like.
This is something on the side, something
if you're interested in something as a
bonus. So if you want, I can show you
how I did it, and how you can replicate
it. Um, copy and paste. This is my what
my Discord server looks like. So uh,
that's the name of it, and there are 54
mentees right now. There's a bit more
this public section where I have student
wins, public chat where everyone can
chat, announcements, leaderboards,
streaks. These things are
self-explanatory. And then I also have a
section for paid students, mentees only.
It's for mentorship program students. So
once you pay uh you get access to all
this stuff. So premium course is where
you have the 50 course modules and
retweet circle is where we retweet uh
your post. So let's say you start
completely new, you make a brand new
account, brand new post and you're
struggling to get views. So what we will
do is that all of us with our big
accounts, we will retweet you. We will
give you a shout out. We'll give you
retweets um so that you can start going
viral ASAP. It's so much easier. And so
that's exactly what I do. When I make a
new account, I retweet from all the big
accounts so that it goes viral
instantly.
Uh we have some mastermind recordings,
group calls, uh case studies of some
accounts, what they're posting, what
product they're doing, exact you know
ins and out of the business.
So this is the exciting part is um the
high income rewards program. So
basically how it works
is once you start making 10K per month,
you join the mentorship, you make sales,
you cross 10K per month threshold, then
I will fly you out here to LA where I'm
in. I'm in Los Angeles right now. So
I'll basically invite you here. I'll
I'll pay for all the flights um you know
everything. celebrate with me in person
because you know I do cherish having
genuine relationship with each one of my
students and I genuinely um you know
this is not only the goal but
expectation for each one of my students
is to come celebrate. He'll pick one
supercar uh for the day and we'll dine
at the tallest and most luxurious
restaurant in the West Coast in Los
Angeles, 71 stories high. Um and we'll
strategize on how to, you know, grow it
to 100k months and beyond. So, this is
the restaurant that I'm talking about.
These are my students. That's me in the
corner, 71 stories high. I did kind of
photoshop my face just to make myself
look a bit cooler, but my face is a
little weird. Anyways, three of my
students, they cross 10K per month and
we take this take them to the tallest
restaurant here. Um, these are the
drinks that we ordered. I can't zoom in.
I guess I can. This is what it looks
like. Very high, very cool place. And I
paid for the entire meal, obviously. Um,
and I drive my students around in the
Lamborghini. These are three Red Bulls.
Um, yeah, at this time I didn't have
like an Aventador Huracan just cuz I
needed to fit four people. So, that's
why I had an SCBM.
Yeah, this is the cool part. 100%
guaranteed. I'm so confident in my
mentorship program that, you know,
everyone succeeds as long as you're
putting in the effort. So, basically, I
have this 90-day guarantee, 100%
satisfactionary money back, which I've
never had to do, but, you know, this is
just what I have. If you're earning less
than $5,000 in sales within 90 days, you
get a full refund, provided that you're
consistently putting in daily work. You
know, you're posting, you're putting in
the work. Obviously, it's not going to
count if you're not putting any effort.
Because sometimes I do have students who
join and then they do not work at all.
They're so lazy. They do not put any
work. And if you're like that, you
should not expect to make any money or
succeed with this business. But if
you're consistently working hard, then I
guarantee you that you'll be making a
lot. And this has never happened. Um,
and that's why I only accept people that
I see real potential in. You know,
obviously I'm going to be putting in a
lot of my time, effort, and focus into
each one of my students, right?
Obviously, it would be a waste of time,
effort, and focus on my behalf if I pour
all this out into you and that you don't
succeed. Like, my mentality is that you
better succeed now that since I'm
investing a lot into you again, this
never happened, this refund, but this is
a worst case scenario. If you make less
than that, then you're putting
consistent work, then you get a full
refund. I'm very confident that this
will never happen, though. Yeah. So if
you want to join, all you have to do is
to fill out this type form. I think this
will be a YouTube video. So there should
be a link in bio or this description. It
looks like this. Just put in a bunch of,
you know, information about yourself,
your name, phone number, email, why
you're interested, and then you can book
a call with me. Book a time, pick a
time, and then we can talk. It will be
me. It won't be a closer. I don't have
any closers for my main offer. You'll be
talking directly with me.
Um, and then text me on Telegram. Uh,
once you've finished that and you're all
set to go. Bonus, I do have YouTube
channel where I have interviews with my
students who are making more than 30K
per month. I also have do a podcast with
other millionaire genzies. So, those who
are making uh millions of dollars. I
interview them so that you can learn and
copy the same. I also have an Instagram
where you can follow. I have a lot of
behind the scenes of my lifestyle, what
my life looks like in general. So, yeah,
that that's there. And anyways, if you
got to the end of this video, if you're
watching this still right now, I applaud
you because you're in the top 99
percentile.